Tuftonian UP001
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tuftonian, 1874 -- 1965; UP001.001; 0.25 Linear Feet; 60 Volumes
  - Tuftonian, October, 1927; UP001.001.029.00001 (Box Volume 29)
  - Tuftonian, January, 1927; UP001.001.029.00002 (Box Volume 29)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1928; UP001.001.029.00003 (Box Volume 29)
  - Tuftonian, June, 1928; UP001.001.029.00004 (Box Volume 29)
  - Tuftonian, August, 1928; UP001.001.029.00005 (Box Volume 29)
    Alumni association meetings; Alumni day; Alumni trustees
  - Tuftonian, January, 1929; UP001.001.030.00002 (Box 30)
    Volume, issue
    3, 1
  - Tuftonian, May, 1929; UP001.001.030.00003 (Box 30)
    3, 3
  - Tuftonian, June, 1929; UP001.001.030.00004 (Box 30)
    3, 4
  - Tuftonian, December, 1929; UP001.001.030.00005 (Box 30)
    4, 1
  - Tuftonian, March, 1930; UP001.001.030.00006 (Box 30)
    4, 2
  - Tuftonian, June, 1930; UP001.001.030.00007 (Box 30)
    4, 3
  - Tuftonian, November, 1930; UP001.001.032.00001 (Box Volume 32)
  - Tuftonian, February, 1931; UP001.001.032.00002 (Box Volume 32)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1931; UP001.001.032.00003 (Box Volume 32)
  - Tuftonian, June, 1931; UP001.001.032.00004 (Box Volume 32)
  - Tuftonian, November, 1931; UP001.001.033.00001 (Box Volume 33)
  - Tuftonian, January, 1932; UP001.001.033.00002 (Box Volume 33)
  - Tuftonian, March, 1932; UP001.001.033.00003 (Box Volume 33)
  - Tuftonian, May, 1932; UP001.001.033.00004 (Box Volume 33)
  - Tuftonian, November, 1932; UP001.001.034.00001 (Box Volume 34)
  - Tuftonian, February, 1933; UP001.001.034.00002 (Box Volume 34)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1933; UP001.001.034.00003 (Box Volume 34)
  - Tuftonian, June, 1933; UP001.001.034.00004 (Box Volume 34)
  - Tuftonian, December, 1933; UP001.001.035.00001 (Box Volume 35)
    Contains an index for vols. 7 and 8.
  - Tuftonian, January, 1934; UP001.001.035.00002 (Box Volume 35)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1934; UP001.001.035.00003 (Box Volume 35)
  - Tuftonian, June, 1934; UP001.001.035.00004 (Box Volume 35)
  - Tuftonian, November, 1934; UP001.001.036.00001 (Box Volume 36)
  - Tuftonian, January, 1935; UP001.001.036.00002 (Box Volume 36)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1935; UP001.001.036.00003 (Box Volume 36)
  - Tuftonian, June, 1935; UP001.001.036.00004 (Box Volume 36)
  - Tuftonian, December, 1935; UP001.001.037.00001 (Box Volume 37)
  - Tuftonian, February, 1936; UP001.001.037.00002 (Box Volume 37)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1936; UP001.001.037.00003 (Box Volume 37)
  - Tuftonian, June, 1936; UP001.001.037.00004 (Box Volume 37)
  - Tuftonian, November, 1936; UP001.001.038.00001 (Box Volume 38)
  - Tuftonian, February, 1937; UP001.001.038.00002 (Box Volume 38)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1937; UP001.001.038.00003 (Box Volume 38)
  - Tuftonian, June, 1937; UP001.001.038.00004 (Box Volume 38)
  - Tuftonian, Fall, 1937; UP001.001.039.00001 (Box Volume 39)
  - Tuftonian, Winter, 1938; UP001.001.039.00002 (Box Volume 39)
  - Tuftonian, Spring, 1938; UP001.001.039.00003 (Box Volume 39)
  - Tuftonian, Fall, 1938; UP001.001.040.00001 (Box Volume 40)
  - Tuftonian, Winter, 1939; UP001.001.040.00002 (Box Volume 40)
  - Tuftonian, Spring, 1939; UP001.001.040.00003 (Box Volume 40)
  - Tuftonian, Fall, 1939; UP001.001.041.00001 (Box Volume 41)
  - Tuftonian, Winter, 1940; UP001.001.041.00002 (Box Volume 41)
  - Tuftonian, Spring, 1940; UP001.001.041.00003 (Box Volume 41)
  - Tuftonian, November, 1940; UP001.001.042.00001 (Box Volume 42)
    [Abbott, Freeland K. (1942)] American perspectives (poem). pp. 18-19.
  - Tuftonian, January, 1941; UP001.001.042.00002 (Box Volume 42)
  - Tuftonian, March, 1941; UP001.001.042.00003 (Box Volume 42)
    [Alexander, Rose] A Note on "Thunder Rock"; Commentary on play given by Pen, Paint and Pretzels.
  - Tuftonian, May, 1941; UP001.001.042.00004 (Box Volume 42)
  - Tuftonian, November, 1941; UP001.001.043.00001 (Box Volume 43)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Abbott, Feeland K. (1942)] Shuddering New England. pp. 41-42.
  - Tuftonian, January, 1942; UP001.001.043.00002 (Box Volume 43)
  - Tuftonian, March, 1942; UP001.001.043.00003 (Box Volume 43)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Abbott, Donald G. "Letter Home" (Freshman English) p. 119.
  - Tuftonian, May, 1942; UP001.001.043.00004 (Box Volume 43)
  - Tuftonian, November, 1942; UP001.001.044.00001 (Box Volume 44)
  - Tuftonian, January, 1943; UP001.001.044.00002 (Box Volume 44)
    Abbott, Donald G. "I Can't Decide" pp. 85-86
  - Tuftonian, March, 1943; UP001.001.044.00003 (Box Volume 44)
    Tufts men of science [Leonard Carmicheal; Amos E. Dolbear; Arthur Micheal; Norbert Weiner; Arthur Lamb.]
  - Tuftonian, May, 1943; UP001.001.044.00004 (Box Volume 44)
    Phyllis D. Ahern. The Quartette Rehearses. (poem); To Stephen Vincent Benet (poem).
  - Tuftonian, Fall, 1943; UP001.001.045.00001 (Box Volume 45)
  - Tuftonian, Summer, 1944; UP001.001.045.00002 (Box Volume 45)
  - Tuftonian, Fall, 1944; UP001.001.045.00003 (Box Volume 45)
  - Tuftonian, Spring, 1945; UP001.001.046.00001 (Box Volume 46)
  - Tuftonian, January, 1946; UP001.001.046.00002 (Box Volume 46)
  - Tuftonian, Spring, 1946; UP001.001.046.00003 (Box Volume 46)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. The Alexander Bain Society by Robert C. Givler.
  - Tuftonian, Volume VI, Number 1, 1947; UP001.001.047.00001 (Box Volume 47)
  - Tuftonian, Volume VI, Number 2, 1947; UP001.001.047.00002 (Box Volume 47)
  - Tuftonian, January, 1948; UP001.001.047.00003 (Box Volume 47)
  - Tuftonian, Volume VI, Number 4, ca., 1949; UP001.001.047.00004 (Box Volume 47)
  - Tuftonian, Volume 7, Number 1, ca., 1949; UP001.001.048.00001 (Box Volume 48)
  - Tuftonian, Volume 7, Number 2, ca., 1949; UP001.001.048.00002 (Box Volume 48)
  - Tuftonian, Volume 8, Number 1, ca., 1950; UP001.001.048.00003 (Box Volume 48)
  - Tuftonian, January, 1951; UP001.001.049.00001 (Box Volume 49)
  - Tuftonian, October, 1951; UP001.001.049.00002 (Box Volume 49)
  - Tuftonian, March, 1952; UP001.001.049.00003 (Box Volume 49)
  - Tuftonian, June, 1952; UP001.001.049.00004 (Box Volume 49)
  - Tuftonian, January, 1953; UP001.001.050.00001 (Box Volume 50)
  - Tuftonian, February, 1953; UP001.001.050.00002 (Box Volume 50)
  - Tuftonian, Spring, 1953; UP001.001.050.00003 (Box Volume 50)
  - Tuftonian, Summer, 1953; UP001.001.050.00004 (Box Volume 50)
    [Administration] The Administration Speaks. (Wessell, Nils Y.) p. 29.
  - Tuftonian, Christmas, 1953; UP001.001.051.00001 (Box Volume 51)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1954; UP001.001.051.00002 (Box Volume 51)
  - Tuftonian, June, 1954; UP001.001.051.00003 (Box Volume 51)
  - Tuftonian, Spring, 1955; UP001.001.051.00004 (Box Volume 51)
  - Tuftonian, May, 1954; UP001.001.051.00005 (Box Volume 51)
  - Tuftonian, Fall, 1955; UP001.001.052.00001 (Box Volume 52)
    Alfred Ainbinder "The Aging and the Young".
  - Tuftonian, April, 1956; UP001.001.052.00002 (Box Volume 52)
  - Tuftonian, Fall, 1956; UP001.001.052.00003 (Box Volume 52)
  - Tuftonian, Winter, 1957; UP001.001.052.00004 (Box Volume 52)
    Robert Frost issue.
  - Tuftonian, Spring, 1957; UP001.001.052.00005 (Box Volume 52)
    [Abbott, Isabel (Mrs. Freeland K.)] Hawthorne and Emerson Discuss "Long Day's Journey into Night." pp. 26-28
  - Tuftonian, December, 1957; UP001.001.053.00001 (Box Volume 53)
    Alfred Ainbinder "The Lovers" (prize poem).
  - Tuftonian, March, 1958; UP001.001.053.00002 (Box Volume 53)
  - Tuftonian, May, 1958; UP001.001.053.00003 (Box Volume 53)
    Thomas Ahern. Blue Jazz and Poetry.
  - Tuftonian, December, 1958; UP001.001.054.00001 (Box Volume 54)
    [Allen, Judith] Green with Gore.
  - Tuftonian, April, 1959; UP001.001.054.00002 (Box Volume 54)
  - Tuftonian, May, 1959; UP001.001.054.00003 (Box Volume 54)
  - Tuftonian, December, 1959; UP001.001.055.00001 (Box Volume 55)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1960; UP001.001.055.00002 (Box Volume 55)
  - Tuftonian, May, 1960; UP001.001.055.00003 (Box Volume 55)
  - Tuftonian, October, 1960; UP001.001.056.00001 (Box Volume 56)
  - Tuftonian, February, 1961; UP001.001.056.00002 (Box Volume 56)
  - Tuftonian, May, 1961; UP001.001.056.00003 (Box Volume 56)
  - Tuftonian, November, 1961; UP001.001.057.00001 (Box Volume 57)
  - Tuftonian, February, 1962; UP001.001.057.00002 (Box Volume 57)
  - Tuftonian, May, 1962; UP001.001.057.00003 (Box Volume 57)
  - Tuftonian, October, 1962; UP001.001.057.00004 (Box Volume 57)
  - Tuftonian, January, 1963; UP001.001.057.00005 (Box Volume 57)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1963; UP001.001.057.00006 (Box Volume 57)
  - Tuftonian, May, 1963; UP001.001.057.00007 (Box Volume 57)
  - Tuftonian, November, 1963; UP001.001.057.00008 (Box Volume 57)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1964; UP001.001.057.00009 (Box Volume 57)
  - Tuftonian, December, 1964; UP001.001.057.00010 (Box Volume 57)
  - Tuftonian, The Centennial Issue, February, 1965; UP001.001.057.00011 (Box Volume 57)
  - Tuftonian, May, 1965; UP001.001.057.00012 (Box Volume 57)